const pheobeQuestions = [{
        question: "After Phoebe misses out on the London trip, where does the group try and plan a trip to?",
        a: "Atlantic City",
        b: "New Jersey",
        c: "The Hamptons",
        d: "Brooklyn",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        question: "Why do Phoebe and Mike break up?",
        a: "His parents do not apporve",
        b: "He is allergic to cats",
        c: "He never wants to get married",
        d: "She wants to go back to David",
        answer: "C",

    },
    {
        question: "Which TV Network Did Phoebe Hate?",
        a: "PBS",
        b: "CNN",
        c: "BBC",
        d: "ITV",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        question: "How Much Money Did Phoebe Get After Finding A Thumb In Her Soda?",
        a: "$2000",
        b: "$3000",
        c: "$5000",
        d: "$7000",
        answer: "D",
    }
]
const joeyQuestions = [{
        question: "What's the name of Joey's imaginary friend?",
        a: "Chris",
        b: "Matt",
        c: "Maurice",
        d: "Jeff",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        question: "When he turned 30, Joey cried like a baby. He cried again at the 30th birthday celebrations of some of the other friends. Who were they?",
        a: "Chandler and Rachel",
        b: "Ross and Rachel",
        c: "Chandler and Pheobe",
        d: "Ross and Monica",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin pal?",
        a: "Cuddly",
        b: "Sleepy",
        c: "Kissy",
        d: "Hugsy",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        question: "What was Joey's last line on the show?",
        a: "Shall we get coffee?",
        b: "Sure, where?",
        c: "I guess so",
        d: "I'm hungry",
        answer: "B",
    },
]
const rachelQuestions = [{
        question: "Who Did Rachel Almost Marry?",
        a: "Harry",
        b: "Barry",
        c: "Jerry",
        d: "Perry",
        answer: "B",
    }, {
        question: "How Long Was The Letter She Wrote For Ross?",
        a: "18 pages, front and back",
        b: "15 pages, front and back",
        c: "19 pages, front and back",
        d: "13 pages, front and back",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        question: "What Weird Fear Did Rachel Have?",
        a: "things touching her feet",
        b: "things touching her knees",
        c: "things touching her elbows",
        d: "things touching her hair",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        question: "What Pet Did Rachel Buy That Freaked Everyone Out?",
        a: "A rat",
        b: "A snake",
        c: "A hairless cat",
        d: "A ferret",
        answer: "C",
    },
]
const rossQuestions = [{
        question: "What Was The Name Of The Student Ross Dated In Season 6?",
        a: "Annabelle",
        b: "Isabelle",
        c: "Elizabeth",
        d: "Eliza",
        answer: "C",
    }, {
        question: "How Many Times Has Ross Been Divorced?",
        a: "2",
        b: "3",
        c: "4",
        d: "5",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        question: "What Was The Surname Of Emily, Ross' Second Wife?",
        a: "Wheeler",
        b: "Wilson",
        c: "Willis",
        d: "Waltham",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        question: "What Was The Name Of The Band Chandler And Ross Formed In High School?",
        a: "Way, No way",
        b: "Way, Yes way",
        c: "Way, There is a way",
        d: "Way, Some way",
        answer: "A",
    },
]
const monicaQuestions = [{
        question: "What Are The Name's Of Monica's Parents?",
        a: "Judy and Jack",
        b: "Judy and Joseph",
        c: "Jill and Jack",
        d: "Janet and Jim",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        question: "Who Lived With Monica Before Rachel?",
        a: "Ross",
        b: "Chandler",
        c: "Joey",
        d: "Pheobe",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        question: "What Did Monica's Parents Spend Her Wedding Fund On?",
        a: "Car",
        b: "Beach house",
        c: "Cruise",
        d: "Starting a new business",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        question: "What Did Monica And Chandler Name Their Twins?",
        a: "Jack and Jill",
        b: "Eric and Jaqoline",
        c: "Jack and Erica",
        d: "Eric and Joshephine",
        answer: "C",
    },
]
const chandlerQuestions = [{
        question: "What Is Chandler's Middle Name?",
        a: "Maura",
        b: "Muriel",
        c: "Mary",
        d: "Marybeth",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        question: "Who Does Chandler's Online Date Turn Out To Be?",
        a: "Monica",
        b: "Kathy",
        c: "Janice",
        d: "Joanna",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        question: "Who Does Chandler Realise He Has A Lot In Common With?",
        a: "Mr Heckles",
        b: "Treeger",
        c: "Richard",
        d: "Pete",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        question: "Who Did Chandler Get Trapped In An ATM Vestibule With?",
        a: "Cindy Crawford",
        b: "Winona Ryder",
        c: "Yasmine Bleeth",
        d: "Jill Goodacre",
        answer: "D",
    },
]